Guide to the Le Bayou Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Correspondence, 1937-1964
  - Oberholtzer, E.E.; University of Houston, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Office de Documentation Bibliographique et de Diffusion du Livre Français, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - O’Meara, Maurice A.; Iowa, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Oppitz, René C.; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Osterrath, Jacqueline; Allemagne, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Oswald, Pierre-Jean; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Overland; Talence, France, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - P., Heloise; Florida, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Patch, Ruey Joan, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Pathé Marconi; Paris, France, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Paul, Jallaguier, Lyon, France, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Pénélope; Istanbul, Turkuie, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Periale, Marise; Sefrou, Maroc, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Perkins, Constance; Colorado, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Phalen, Eileen, Houston, Texas, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Philipps, Hosea; Louisiana, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - Pin, Elisée; Boches-de-Rhône, France, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Pirson, Jeanne; Costermansville, Congo, Belgique, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Pohoryles, Bernard M.; New York, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Postmaster; Houston, Texas, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Pousson, Elmer; Texas, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Powell, Charlotte Alva; Michigan, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Premsela, M.-J.; Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Les Prix Annuels de la Maison Poésie, undated (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Le Prix Interfrance de Poésie, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Prix Littéraire Antoine de Rivarol, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Prix Moreas, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Quincy, Edmund; Italie, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Le Quintrec, Charles; Paris, France, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - R., Boyd; California, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - R., Hubert, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Raffalovich, George; Louisiana, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Raveton, Roland; Paris, France, undated (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Ray, Dr.; Texas, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Ratchford, Frances; Texas, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Redman, Jr., Harry; Wisconsin, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Reichlin, Margu Yvonne; Paris, France, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Reitman, Edouard; New York, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Renard, Jean Claude; Paris, France, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Richard, Robert Veibel; Argentina, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Richer, Jacques; Paris, France, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Rickey, H. Wynn; Texas, 1947-1948, 1950-1951, 1953-1958 (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Ridge, George Ross; Georgia, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Rieder, V.; France, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Riendeau, Adrienne; Rhode Island, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Ridge, George Ross; Georgia, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - Roelandt, L.; Belgique, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Rolin, Henri; New York, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Rollin, Mila; Spain, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Romains, Gabrielle; Nanterre, France, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Romus, André; Liége, Belgique, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Roseremark, Solange; Paris, France (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Roussel, H.; Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Roux, Jacqueline L.; New York, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Royet-Journoud, Claude; London, England, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Rubissono, Helen, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Ruch; Warsaw, Poland, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Sabartier, Robert; Roanne, France, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Saintonge, J.A.; Belgique, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Saylor, Darien; Houston, Texas, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Scarfe, Francis; England, undated (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Schigman, Jeanne, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Schiritta, C.; Roanne, France, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Schultz, Anna, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Seghers, Pierre; Paris, France, 1946-1954 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Shay, Violet Brown; New Orléans, Louisiana, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Siegfried, André; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Silin, Charles I.; New Orléans, Louisiana, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Simmons, Nancy; New York, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Simon, Louis; France, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Simon, Madeleine; Houston, Texas, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Maxwell A.; Tennessee, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Soniat, Lucile; New Orléans, Louisiana, 1939-1941, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sor, Daniel; Paris, France, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sorel, Claude; Paris, France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Soudany, Jameleddine; Tunisie, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Spuric, Shirley; Houston, Texas, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Spurlin, Paul; Louisana, 1941-1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Stanely, Madeleine; New York, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Strowski, Fortunant; Paris, France, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Souvessance, J.; France, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Syndicat National des Editeurs-Exportateurs de Publications Françaises; Paris, France, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Szécheny, François de; Pennsylvania, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Thériot, Marie; Louisiana, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Thérive, André; Paris, France; Carrefour, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Thiroux, Jules; Valenciennes, France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Thirrerge, Héléne; Maine, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Tinayre, Madame Marcelle; Paris, France, 1937, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Tinkie, Lon; Texas, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Triger, Fernand; Nantes, France, 1958, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tolentino, Justo P.; Manilla, Philippines, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Tournebize, Jean M.; France, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Tuckerman, Elise; New York, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Uffenbeck, L.A.; New York, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Unimuse; Belgique, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Union Culturelle Française; Paris, France, 1955, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - United States Information Agency; Washington, 1954, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Urruty, Jean; Ile. Maurice, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Valois, Marie; New York, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Van der Wal; François; California, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Verne, Jules; Houston, Texas; Aronson Collection, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Vinatrel, Guy; Paris, France, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Vinson, Elkins and Weems, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Vulfsons, H.; New York, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Submissions, 1937-1963
  This series consists of roughly 3 boxes of material that was submitted for publication in Le Bayou, from its inception to when it stopped publication in 1963. These folders include fiction, poetry, essays, and book reviews, and many of their authors submitted material for many years. It is organized alphabetically, and then by date.
  - General, 1937-1963
    This subseries consists of material submitted for publication in Le Bayou, from its inception to when it stopped publication in 1963. It is organized alphabetically, and then by date.
    - Allart, Hortense, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Amiel, J. Henri; New Orléans, Louisiana, 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Binder, Aimée; New Orléans, Louisiana, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Bocquet, Léon; Paris, France, 1948-1949, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Brochon, René; Léognan, France, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Chincholle, Jeanne; Denver, Colorado, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - De Bordeu, Charles; Posthume, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Dunbar, Paul Lawrence, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Elot, Maryse; Puerto Rico, 1948-1963 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Emié, Louis; France, 1951, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Engerland, Roland; La Fabrice, France, 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Evrard, Madame Andree; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - “Exegese des Chimeras”, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Euloge, René; Marrakech, Maroc, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Faillant, Paule; Paris, France, 1945, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Fanchette, Régis; Ile Maurice, 1949, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Farges, Michel; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Fédou, A.J.; Moux Aude, France, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Fenaux, Guy; Belgique, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Fiore, Anne; Washington D.C, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Fiorentino, Luigi; Italie, 1948, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Fleurisson, René; Angoulême, France, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Fombeure, Maurice; France, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Fonda, Carlo; Port Arthur, Ontario, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Fontnouvelle, P.; New York, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Forot, Charles; St. Félicien, France, 1948-1956 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Foucher, Jean-Pierre; France, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Foulon, Roger; Thuin, Belgique, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Fournel, Gilles; Boisgervilly, France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Franco, S.; Casablanca, Maroc, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Gabriel, Pierre; Condom, France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Galichet, Georges; Limoges, France, 1958-1959, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Galinier, Dr. Georges; Sétif, Algérie, 1951, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Gambier, Gerard; Liége, Belgique, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Garibaldi, A.; Portugal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Gascht, André; Belgique, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Gastaldi, Santiago; Montevideo, Uruguay, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Gaud, Robert; Annonay, France, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Geeraert, Robert-Lucien; Tournai, Belgique, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Gerville-Réache, Lucien; Guadeloupe, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Gigot, Jean, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Gille, Jules; Marcinelle, Belgique, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Glénisson, E.; Illinois, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Godefroy, Albert; Fleurus, Belgique, 1960, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Goldet, Cécile; Paris, France, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Gorini, Mario; Pesaro, Italie, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Got, Armand; Bordeaux, France, 1948-1963 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Gousset, Gabriel; Rabat, Maroc, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Goyen, William, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Gregh, Fernand; Paris, France, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Grilhé, Gilette; Paris, France, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Gros, Eugène; St. Etienne, France, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Grosclaude, Pierre; Paris, France, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Grubbs, Diane; Ohio, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Gruesse, Christiane; Algiers, Algérie, 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Guex-Gastambide, Francis; Dreux, France, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Guibal, Louis, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Guitland, Marcel; Perpignan, France, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Guirande, Paul, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Guy, Alain; Toulouse, France, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Haggard, Grace H.; Houston, Texas, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Haloche, Maurice; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Haristoy, Michel; Bordeaux, France, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Harrison, Benjamin I.; Mississippi, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Hébert, Anne; Québec, Canada, 1941-1942, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Hébert, Maurice; Québec, Canada, 1938-1955 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Hébert, Pierre; Paris, France, 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Hébert, Rodolphe-Louis; Arizona, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Hennart, Marcel; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Henriot, Emile; Paris, France, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Hercourt, Jean; Genéve, Suisse, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Hercoult, Michel; Villepinte, France, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Heurtin, J.; Paris, France, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Heywood, Terence; Arundel, Sussex, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - House, Boyce; Texas, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Huby, Simone; Paris, France, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Humphrey, George; New York, 1949-1963 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Humphries, Flora; Texas, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Ichon, Franz J.; Paris, France, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Innox, Jacques; California, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Izzard, H.W.; England, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Jack, Muriel; Boulogne-sur-Seine, France, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Jacot, Claude; New York, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Jeannenot, Georgette; Besançon, France, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Jobin, Antoine; Michigan, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Joignet, Marcelle; Tours, France, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Josia, Angelo; Italie, 1949-1951, 1954, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Jouglet, René, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Jour, Jean; Liége, Belgique, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Juin, Hubert; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Jullien, Casimir; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Junod, Jean-Michel; Suisse, 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Karas, Denise; Liége, Belgique, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Katz, Joseph; California, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Kervran, R.; France, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Kiibler, Dennis W., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Kindler, Leonard; New York, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Klein, Jean-Pierre; Paris, France, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Kling, Georges; Indo-China, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Kosmann, Claude; Paris, France, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Kowalski, Roger; Lyon, France, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Lacroix, Raymond; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Laffon, Rafael; Sevilla, Spain, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Lambert, France; Paris, France, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Lambert, Pierre; Paris, France, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Lamireau, Gilbert, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Langellier, Paul; New York, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Landau, Charlotte Brebant; New York, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - L’anselme, Jean; Savigny, France, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Lapointe, Gatien; Québec, Canada, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Larrive, Georges; Paris, France, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Laurence, Evelyne; Genève, Suisse, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Laurent, Patrice; Paris, France, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Lavaud, Guy; Poissy, France, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Lavaud, Guy; Poissy, France, 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Lavaud, Guy; Poissy, France, 1954-1958 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Laveau, Andrè; Tours, France, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Lauer, Ginette, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Laurière, Emile; Paris, France, 1937-1954 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Lebert, Eugène M.; Massachusetts, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Lebois, André; Nantes, France, 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Lebrau, Jean; Moux, France, 1945-1956 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Le Chevalier, André; New York, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Leclére, Jacques; Belgian Congo, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Lecomte du Nouy, Pierre; New York, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Le Cordier, Roland; Rueil-Malmaison, France, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Lecrique, Camile; Mohon, France, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Leftwich, James A.; California, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Leger, Germaine; France, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Le Gouic, Gérard; Fort Lamy, Tchad, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Legrand, Paul; Montrèal, Canada, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Lemieux-Levesque, Alice; New Hampshire, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Le Mercier d’Erm, Camile; France, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Lemon, Hilda, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Lenemen, Félix; New York, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Lenoble, Raymond-Jean; Gosselies, Belgique, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Leon, Felix; Amsterdam, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Leon, Jean-Michel; Paris, France, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Leoni, Dr. Ilde; Rhode Island, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Le Page, Jacques; France, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Le Tarare, Jean-Paul, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Le Travailler, 1944-1955 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Leuck, René-Georges; Paris, France, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Levy-Valle; Maroc, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Libbrecht, Géo; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1949-1962 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Linze, Georges; Liège, Belgique, 1958-1962 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Linze, Jacques G.; Grivegnée, Belgique, 1957-1963 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Lippens, Louis; Linselles, France, 1954-1959 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Lobet, Marcel; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Lochac, Emmanuel; France, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Lopez, Enrique Martinez; University of Houston, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Lorris, Robert; Tournai, Belgique, 1954-1957 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Lossier, Jean G.; Genève, Suisse, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Lot, Fernand; Paris, France, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Loubière, Pierre; Rodez, France, 1948-1963 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Louden, Catherine; Houston, Texas, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Lowe, Robert W.; Arizona, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Lucas, Wilfred; Paris, France, 1948-1961 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Lupon, Paul Bernard; Annecey, France, 1952, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Mabry, Nicole; New York, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Mackey, Helen; New York, 1943-1960 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - McClure, Anne; Washington D.C., 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - McLay, Jeannine; Montréal, Canada, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - McLendon, Will; University of Houston, 1955, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Soeur Madeleine; St. Matthew’s School; Louisiana, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Magnette, Eloi; Belgique, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Mamet, Suzanne C.; Ile Maurice, 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Manuel, Alex; Washington, 1950-1965 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Marants, M., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Mari, Paul; Nice, France, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Markale, Jean, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Marshall, Robert; New York, 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Marsolle, Edward; Guadeloupe, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Martel, André; Vincennes, France, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Marti, Delphine; Paris, France, 1948-1962 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Martin, Jacques; Carcassonne, France, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Martin, Jacques; Limoux, France, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Mary, André; France, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Matthijs, Georges-Marie; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1947-1951 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Masson, Mary; (Sauvabelin, Marie); Paris, France, 1954-1957 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Maton, Jean; (Tristan Maya); France, 1950-1963 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Mauget, Irénee; La Celle de Saint-Cloud; France, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Maurette, Michel; Clos St. Michel Caux et Sauzens, France, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Maurice-Amour, Lila; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Mauroc, Daniel; Paris, France, undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Maurois, André; France, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Menard, René; Paris, France, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Mermier, Guy; Michigan, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Mervial, Kees; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Message, André; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Métérié, Alphonse; Suisse, undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Metzinger, Jean, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Meuriche, Auguste, undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Michael, Roger; France, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Micheloud, Pierrette; Lausanne, Suisse, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Eugenia; Houston, Texas, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Milosz, L.; Paris, France, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Minne, Julles; Belgique, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Mirjean, Serge, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Mitchell, Bonner; Missouri, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Mohamed, Khair Eddine; Agadir, Maroc, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Molaine, Pierre; Lyon, France, 1951-1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Mongruel, Georgina; Brésil, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Moore, 1949-1950, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Morange, Hélène; Chauriat, France, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Moriame, Victor; Paris, France, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Morini-Comby, Jean; Montpellier, France, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Moussariè, Pierre; Aurillac, France, 1948, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Musa, Gilde; Italie, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Musin, Louis; Belgique, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Mustapha, Nissaboury; Casablanca, Maroc, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Myers, Rowland; Texas, 1942-1951 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Nantier, Etienne; New York, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Nazariantz, Hrand; Arménie, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Nègres Américains; Bibliographies, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Nelson, Alice Dunbar, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Nettie, M.; Paris, France, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Noppeney, Marcel; Luxembourg, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Noth, Ernst Erich; New York, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Noth, Ernst Erich; (Books Abroad); Oklahoma, 1949-1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Ominus, Jean; France, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Palgen, Paul; Liège, Belgique, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Pallister, Janis; Maine, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Payer, André; Paris, France, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pechyrand, Roger; Montvalent, France, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Perot, Marie-Louise, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Perruchot, Henri; Paris, France, 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Petit, Marcel; Rabat, Maroc, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Pétronio, Arthur; Les Taillades, France, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Peyre, Sully-André; Mûrevigne, France, 1947-1953 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Peyssou, Maurice; Bordeaux, France, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Philipps, Hosea; Louisiana, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Picard, Roger; New York, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Pichery, Ronan, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Piare, Jacques; Angers, France, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Pize, Louis; Lyon, France, 1948-1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Plante, Jean-Paul; Québec, Canada, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Pohl, Jacques; Bruxelles, 1952-1955, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Pohl, Pierre; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Poilvetle Guenn, Jean; St. Brieuc, France, 1947-1963 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Poole, Mary Edna; Houston, Texas, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Poyet, A.; Le Puy, France, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Quinot, Raymond; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948-1954 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Reboux, Paul; Nice, France, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Raes, Florent; Roulers, Belgique, 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Raes, Liliane; Belgique, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Ragon, Michel; Paris, France, 1948-1954 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Ramos, Jorge; Lisbon, Portugal, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Ramos, Rolando; Puerto Rico, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Ranchon, Paul; Paris, France, 1940-1948 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Ravier, Jehanne; Uchaud, France, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Redman, Harry; Wisconsin, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Regard, Jean; Belgique, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Rémy, Rêva; Monstaganem, Algérie, 1955-1963 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Renoux, Isaïe; Carthage, Tunisie, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Richards, M. L.; New Jersey, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Richter, Bodo; Philadelphia, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Riendeau, Adrienne; Rhode Island, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Robert, Michel; Massachusetts, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Robert, Michel; Massachusetts, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Robert, Michel; Massachusetts, 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Robert, Michel; Massachusetts, 1951-1961 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Robic, Paul Alexis; France, undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Rodenbach, André; Gand, Belgique, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 72)